CHRISTINA LU UX/UI Designer

www.christinalu.design luchristina7@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a financial reporter turned UX designer with 1 year of visual and UX design experience, 4 years of data analysis experience, and 5 years of self-taught web design (graphic design/HTML/CSS) knowledge. I use research analysis, visuals, and design feedback to create functional and appealing products.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE DESIGNER

Production (Visual) Designer

Nov 2019

 Utilized client artifacts and branding guides along with the content strategy document to conceptualize an investor relations page for a medicinal corporation's website within the given 3-day deadline.

BLOC

UX Designer Apprentice

Aug 2018 - Jun 2019

- Applied an end to end product design process to build desktop and mobile designs using research data, product strategy, iteration, and testing to provide solutions to pain points
- Defined problems, constraints, and needs for each project resulting in strategic concepts
- Met with a senior level designer weekly to discuss design critiques and receive feedback necessary for future iterations

PIONEER SQUARE ADVISORS

Senior Financial Reporting Associate

Jan 2019 - Present

- Effectively communicates and collaborates with internal, external, and cross-functional teams to handle client obligations resulting in happy clients
- Solves clients' problems by creating custom data reports with data displayed strategically in a way that is easy for the client to understand

EDUCATION

Nov 2019 - Present LearnUI.Design

UI Design

Aug 2018 - Jun 2019 Bloc

UX Design Certificate

California State University, Sacramento

Aug 2010 - May 2015

B.S. Business Administration (Finance)

SKILLS

UX design, web design, graphic design, visual design, userflows, storyboards, wireframes, mockups, responsive design, user testing, prototypes, A/B testing, communication, web and mobile design

TOOLS

Sketch, Figma, Adobe XD, Illustrator, Photoshop, InVision, HTML, CSS, Maze, UsabilityHub, Abstract, Zeplin